Okay, Ross.
好吧，羅斯
I realize that you didn't expect to walk in and see that, but..
我知道你不想進來看到這個
- Let me explain, okay? - We weren't doing anything!
-可是……聽我解釋好嗎？ -我們什麼都沒做！
Rach, he just saw us.
瑞秋，他看到了
But what you saw, that is the extent of it, okay? One kiss.
但你所看到的，就是全部的 知道嗎?僅僅一個吻而已
- That's a lie! We also kissed in Barbados. - Dude, chill!
-不，天吶，你在說謊。我們在巴貝多就吻過了。 -哥們兒，真掃興！
Okay, we also kissed in Barbados..
好吧，我們在巴貝多也吻過
but we didn't plan it. The only reason that that happened..
可我們沒想那樣，知道嗎？ 發生這件事的唯一原因
was because I saw you kiss Charlie.
是我看見你吻查莉了。
Yeah, you started it! I have got to chill.
對，是你開始的！ 我想過要冷卻下來。
Look, we probably should have talked to you about this before it ever happened.
好吧，我們或許應該在事情 發生之前跟你說
- But.. - Oh, we feel so terrible about this, Ross.
-可是…… -我們對於這感到非常害怕，羅斯
Yeah. But it did happen.
是, 對，可它確實發生了
So..
所以……
Ross?
羅斯？
Can we just close the door?
我們可以關上門了麼？
The One Where Ross In Fine
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Ross, say something.
羅斯, 說點什麼。
Anything.
什麼都行。
So you two are..?
所以說你們倆……？
- Yeah. - Yeah.
-是。 -是。
And have you had..?
那你們有沒有……呃？
- No. No, no, no. - No. No.
-沒，沒 -沒有。
But if I hadn't walked in here, would you..?
可如果我沒進來的話，你們會不會……？
Probably.. No. No.
也許。 不, 不會!
Ross, this is not how we wanted you to find out about this.
Ross，我們本來沒想讓你 以這種方式發現。
You have every right to go nuts.
你有權力抓狂。
I'm not going nuts. Do you see me going nuts?
我不會抓狂的。你看我抓狂了?
No, but you know what I mean.
不，可你知道我的意思。
If you two are happy..
如果你們倆開心
then I'm happy for you.
我也會為你們開心。
I'm fine.
我沒事！
- Really? - Absolutely.
-真的？ -當然。
I'm fine.
我沒事！
Totally fine.
完全沒事！
I don't know why it's coming out all loud and squeaky..
我不知道為什麼我的聲音又大又尖
because, really, I'm fine.
不過說真的。我沒事。
I'm not saying I wasn't a little surprised to see you guys kissing.
我不是說我看見你們接吻一點也不吃驚
I mean, at first I was like:
我是說，開始我有點……
But now that I've had time to absorb it..
不過現在我已經開始接受
Loving this.
喜歡了。
- Ross.. - It's all working out.
- 羅斯... -都解決了！
Me and Charlie. And you two.
我和查莉，還有你們倆。
- You know what we should do? - Calm ourselves?
-知道我們應該幹什麼嗎？ -冷靜下來？
No.
不。
We should all have dinner.
我們應該一起吃頓飯。
Yes, we'll do it tomorrow night. I'll cook!
對，我們明天晚上就吃。我來掌勺！
Look, don't you think that would be a little weird?
呃，你不覺得那樣太怪了嗎？
Weird? What? What's weird?
怪？為什麼?哪兒怪了？
The only thing weird would be if someone didn't like Mexican food..
如果有人不喜歡墨西哥菜才是唯一的怪事
because I'm making fajitas!
因為我會做法加它！！ (法加它：一種開胃點心)
I do like fajitas.
我非常喜歡法加它。
God, this adoption stuff is so overwhelming.
天吶，領養這件事真讓人無法抵抗。
There's inter-country adoption, dependency adoption.
有跨國領養，從屬領養……
There's so many ways to go, and this is, like, the biggest decision of our lives.
有這麼多方法 這就像我們一生中最大的決定。
There's a hair in my coffee.
我咖啡裡有頭髮。
Hey, guys.
嗨，夥計們！
Have you seen Frank Jr.? He's meeting me here with the triplets.
嗨，你們看見小弗蘭克了嗎 他要帶著他的三胞胎來看我。
It's funny, every time you say "triplets"..
知道嗎，太有意思了。每次你說「三胞胎」
I think of three hot, blond 19-year-olds.
我馬上就想到三個火辣的19歲金髮女郎。
That's sweet.
想的美
Drink your hair.
喝你的頭髮吧。
Hey, what's all this stuff?
嘿，這些是什麼？
They're brochures from different adoption agencies.
哦，這些是我們從不同的 領養中心找來的小冊子。
Babies! Oh, this one is so cute.
哦，小孩子！ 哦，這個好可愛
Get this one.
就要這個！
That's not really how it works.
這不是這麼用的。
- Oh, how does it work? - I don't know!
-噢，那這個呢？ -我不知道！
If you're having a hard time, you should talk to my friends..
好吧，如果你們遇到什麼困難 可以跟我的朋友們談談
Bill and Colleen. They adopted a kid. I'm sure they'd help you.
比爾和克琳.  他們領養了個孩子，肯定會幫你們的。
Thanks, that would be great.
謝謝，這太好了。
Hey, honey, wouldn't that be great?
嘿，老公，是不是很棒？
All right, all right. Remember what we talked about.
好吧，好吧，好吧。 記住我們剛說的。
When we're in a public place, there are certain rules.
在公共場合，要有一定的規矩。
That's not what we talked about!
我們不是這麼說的！
- Hi, Frank. - Hi.
-嗨！弗蘭克。 -嗨！
- Good to see you. - Good to see you too.
-見到你真好。 -我也一樣。
- Hi, Frank. - Hi. Hey, how you doing?
-嗨，弗蘭克. -嗨，過得怎麼樣？
Oh, my goodness, they've all gotten so big. Which one is which again?
哦，天吶，他們都這麼大了！ 哪個是哪個啊？
Well, that's Frank Jr. Jr..
哦，那個從那個女士包裡
pulling the tampons out of the lady's purse.
扯出棉球來的是小小弗蘭克。
And that's Chandler climbing on Chandler.
錢德在往錢德身上爬。
That's Leslie throwing bagels at him.
萊絲莉在往他身上扔百吉餅。
She's got quite an arm there, doesn't she? Yeah.
她扔的真準啊, 是不是 不是嗎? 是的.
Hey, guys, come give me a hug.
嗨, 夥計們, 來給我個擁抱吧.
Triplets, hug your aunt!
三胞胎, 抱抱你們的阿姨!
It's like hugging fresh cookies.
就像抱著剛出爐的餅乾.
Oh, okay.
噢, 好了.
I'm gonna eat you!
我要吃了你們!
So how you been, Frank?
你怎麼樣, 弗蘭克?
Oh, good, you know. Life is all right. Just taking it day by day.
喔, 還好.你知道 生活還不錯, 一天捱一天
Seems like somebody needs something.
看起來某個人需要你的某個部件.
Oh, no. He's just trying to pull my shoulder out of it's socket.
噢, 不是. 他只是試著 把我的肩膀拽脫臼.
- Oh, my God. - No, it's fine.
- 噢, 我的天. - 沒事, 我很好.
After I black out, he tries to put it back in, so..
我每次都嘗試不讓他那麼做 但他總能成功, 所以..
"Willing to adopt triplets?" No.
想領養三胞胎嗎？ 不！
Can I just say, I know we're doing this for Ross and that's cool.
呃，我要說我們這麼做是為了羅斯 而且這很酷
But if it was up to me, this is not what we'd be doing on our first date.
不過如果讓我來定的話 我們第一次約會的時候不會做這個。
Well, what would we be doing?
那麼，我們會做什麼？
I'd take you out for a romantic night.
我會帶你出去過一個浪漫的夜晚。
Some champagne, fancy dinner, feel you up on the carriage ride home.
有香檳，法國大餐 讓你在馬車上送你回家。
Feel me up?
馬車「上」？
In a carriage.
裡面！
Well, maybe we can have our date later on tonight.
好啦, 也許我們應該晚點再約會.
You know, after this, we'll go back to our apartment..
你知道, 在這之後, 我們會回到我們的房間..
Right, right. Yeah.
對, 對. 是.
We could put on some music, light some candles, and then..
我們放些音樂, 點些蠟燭, 然後..
You want to say feel me up, don't you?
你想說撫摸我, 是不是?
I just think it's something we should do.
我只是覺得這是我們應該做的.
- Hey, Charlie! - Hi.
-嗨，查莉! -嗨
- Hi. - Hey.
-嗨 -嘿
So..
那麼..
- dreading this? - Oh, you bet.
- 害怕嗎? - 噢, 肯定的.
So did you bring a little something for Ross?
所以，你給羅斯帶來點東西？
Actually, it's some stuff you left at my apartment.
實際上……這些是你落在我公寓的。
Well, thanks.
噢，噢，謝謝。
And you can just give me my stuff whenever you want.
知道嗎，你可以隨時把我的東西還給我。
Yeah, I didn't throw any of that out.
好，我什麼都沒丟掉……
I thought I heard voices.
我說我聽到什麼聲音了！
Hi, Charlie.
嗨，查莉!
Hey, Joey.
嗨，喬伊
And, oh, you're gonna have to introduce me to your new girlfriend.
呃……噢！你該向我介紹你的新女朋友。
I'm just kidding. I know Rachel. I know..
我開玩笑的，我認識瑞秋，我認識。
Come. Please come in. Come in.
進來，請進來。進來。
Okay. Well, we brought you some wine.
好的，呃，我們帶來點酒。
That is so thoughtful.
噢！想得真周到。
She's a keeper.
這是她帶來的。
- And what did you bring me, huh? - Actually, that's..
-你又帶來了什麼？ -呃，實際上，這是……
Underwear, a toothbrush..
內褲，牙刷
and a Van Halen CD.
還有范海倫的CD。
I can use all these things!
這些我都用得著！！
Gosh, Ross, you know, you seem a little..
天吶，羅斯，知道嗎，你有點……
What? Fine? Because I am.
什麼？心情很好是嗎？本來我就是！
Aren't you? Aren't you? Aren't..? You see?
你們呢？你們呢？你們呢？ 看到了嗎？
Who else is fine?
還有誰心情好？
Come on.
好吧
Listen. Why don't you try to relax. Maybe have a drink.
聽著，嘿，羅斯。放鬆一點，好嗎？ 來喝點什麼。
You know what, that is a very good idea.
知道嗎？這是個好主意。
I'm gonna go make a pitcher of margaritas.
我要去弄一大罐馬格麗塔酒。
Oh, God.
噢，我的天。
So adorable.
真可愛。
Look at them, sleeping there like angels.
看他們睡得就像天使一樣。
Yeah, I really cherish these moments..
對，我也很珍惜這段時光
because before you know it, they're gonna be awake again.
因為你還沒意識到它的可貴 他們就會醒過來。
Well, they may be a handful..
嗯，他們可能比較難控制
- but they're so cute. - Yeah.
-可他們真得很可愛。 -是啊。
Oh, God, last time I babysat them, they did the funniest thing.
噢，天吶，我最後一次照看他們的時候 他們做了最有意思的事……
I haven't slept in four years.
我已經4年沒睡覺了！
That's a long time.
這麼，這麼久了？
You just don't know how hard it is, Phoebe.
你不知道這又多難，菲比
There's just so many of them.
他們太多了。
You know, two I could handle.
知道嗎，兩個我還能行。
Two's great. You just hold one in each hand.
兩個就太好了。你正一手抱著一個
What do I do when the third one runs at me with his bike helmet on?
可第三個帶著自行車頭盔 朝我跑過來的時候我能怎麼辦？
I got no more hands to protect my area.
我又沒有另一隻手來保護我的要害！
There's three of them, Phoebe. Three.
他們是三個，菲比，三個！
Yeah, I know, Frank.
是，我知道，弗蘭克。
I counted them when they were coming out of my area.
我生他們的時候數過了。
Sometimes, I think that..
有時候我甚至想……
Oh, no, no, no, I can't say it. It's too horrible. No.
哦，不，不，不，我不能說， 太可怕了。不。
What?
什麼？
No, no, I can't.
不，我不能。
Oh, my God, Frank. Are you thinking of leaving?
噢，天吶，弗蘭克，你想擺脫他們？
Because I didn't have those triplets so you could run out on them.
那三胞胎不算是我的 所以你就想要拋棄他們！
Oh, no, I would never do that. No. I just..
噢，不！我永遠不會那麼做。不。
was thinking that, you know, maybe you could take one.
我只是想，你知道嗎 也許你可以帶走一個。
What?
什麼？！
You can't separate them, that's terrible! Which one?
你不能把它們分開！這太可怕了。 哪一個？
Thank you so much for seeing us.
謝謝你能讓我們來。
Phoebe has told us great things about you guys.
菲比跟我們說過你們做的好事了。
Please, we're happy to help.
噢，請進，我們很願意幫忙。
We went through the same thing when we were adopting.
我們領養的時候也經歷過這種事
So a lot of malfunctioning wee-wees and hoo-hoos in this room, huh?
那麼，這間屋子裡也充斥著 wee-wee和hoo-hoo的故障聲了，呃？
I mean, you have a lovely home.
我是說，你們過得很開心。
We appreciate anything you can tell us.
好吧，你們說的一切我們都很感激。
Well, actually, I think this might help.
當然，實際上，我想會有幫助的。
It's pretty much..
這些大概就是
- all the information you need. - Oh, my God.
-你們所需要的所有信息了。 -噢，天吶！
Everything is broken into categories, then cross-referenced.
所有的東西都按類別分開 可以互相引用
Then color-coded to correspond with the forms in the back.
還根據背面的顏色進行了標注。
Thank you.
太感謝了。
I think I just had a tiny orgasm.
我想我剛經歷了一次小高潮。
I know the process is frustrating, but it's so worth it.
我知道過程是讓人沮喪的 不過是值得的。
Adopting Owen was the best thing that ever happened to us.
領養歐文是我們經歷過得最好的事情。
That's great. Can I see the book?
太棒了。我能看看這本書嗎？
You want me to wash my hands first, don't you?
你想讓我先洗手，是不是？
Please. It's just so pretty and white.
這……這個這麼漂亮，而且是白的。
Bathroom is down the hall to your left.
洗手間在走廊那頭，左邊。
I would have told him to do it too.
我也讓他這麼做過。
Can I adopt you?
我能領養你嗎?
- Hey, you must be Owen. - Yeah.
-嗨，你一定是歐文。 -對。
I'm Chandler. Hey, I was in the Scouts too.
我叫錢德。嗨，我也當過童子軍。
- You were? - In fact, my father was a den mother.
-真的？ -當然，實際上我爸爸是童子軍的女訓導員。
You know how to use a compass?
你知道怎麼用指南針嗎？
I have a badge in it.
我得過一枚徽章。
- You do? That's fantastic. - You want to see it?
-真的？真是太棒了！ -你想看嗎？
I'd love to, but I gotta get back to your parents.
當然想，不過我得先回去跟你的父母聊聊。
They're telling us about how they adopted you.
他們在告訴我們怎麼領養你的事。
What?
什麼？！？
怎麼了？
I'm adopted?
我是領養的？
I got nothing.
我什麼都不知道。
I'm adopted?
我是領養的？
No.
不
I didn't say that. I said..
我沒那麼說. 我是說..
you're a doctor.
你是個醫生.
A doctor.
一個醫生.
Hey, doctor, my arm hurts. Can you fix it for me?
嗨, 大夫，我的胳膊疼. 你能幫我修理一下嗎?
I can't believe I'm adopted.
我真不敢相信我是領養的.
So you're not gonna fix my arm?
那..你不準備修理我的胳膊了?
Well, that first batch of margaritas was not so great..
第一批馬格麗塔不是太好
but this second batch is good.
可第二批實在太棒..棒了。
Well, maybe the next batch, we could all get some.
好吧，希望到下一批的時候 我們都能喝一點。
Oh, God, this is fun, isn't it?
噢，夥計們，這很有趣，是嗎？
You know, just the four of us.
知道嗎？就我們四個。
Just hanging.
就這麼呆著。
Dude, are you okay?
夥計，你還好吧？
And when are the fajitas gonna be ready?
法加它什麼時候才能好？
I'm fine, okay? I'm great.
我很好！嘿，我很棒！
I'm just.. I'm just proud of us.
我只是…… 我只是為我們而驕傲。
You know? There's no weirdness, no tension.
一點都不古怪，一點都不緊張。
No awareness.
一點都不清醒。
We make a great foursome. We should do more stuff together.
我們組成一個「四人組」。 我們應該一塊再做些什麼。
Let's take a trip!
哦！ 我們去旅行吧！
We could all go on your boat.
我們可以坐你的船去.
Joey has this amazing sailboat.
喬伊有一艘很棒的帆船.
Actually, Ross, I sold the boat two years ago.
實際上, 羅斯 我兩年前我已經把船賣掉了.
Oh, no. Idiot!
哦, 不. 白癡!
Well, yeah, but I could get another one.
呃, 是的, 不過我可以弄來另外一個.
- This trip sounds great. - Yeah?
- 這個旅行聽起來棒極了. - 是嗎?
Okay, where do you think we can go?
好, 你覺得我們能去哪?
My fajitas!
我的法加它!!
Look, Charlie, I just want you to know..
聽著，查莉，我只想讓你知道。
Ross is just having a little trouble adjusting to the thought of Joey and me.
羅斯還需要時間習慣我跟喬伊在一起。
You know, he normally doesn't drink like this.
知道麼，他一般不這麼喝酒的。
You know what, this is nothing. My father is a raging alcoholic.
噢，你知道嗎？這沒什麼。 我爸爸就是個瘋狂的酒鬼。
I'm sorry, have I made this evening uncomfortable?
噢，對不起 讓你們不舒服了？
Fajitas! Be careful! Very hot plate! Very hot!
法加它!  當心，盤子很燙，盤子很燙！！
Ross, you don't even have oven mitts on.
羅斯，你怎麼沒戴手套！
That is gonna hurt tomorrow.
明天手要疼了！
Okay, well, this is crazy.
好吧，好吧，這太瘋狂了。
We can't seriously be talking about me taking one of your kids, can we?
我們不可能是在嚴肅的討論 我要帶走一個孩子，是嗎？
Oh, no, of course we're not.
不，當然不是。
- That's insane. - I know.
- 太愚蠢了。 - 我知道。
Alice would never go for it.
愛麗絲不會支持的，是嗎？
She's pretty tired too. I think we could get her on board.
噢，我不知道，她也太累了。 我想她可能會入伙的。
Well, just for argument's sake, you know, hypothetically..
好吧，知道嗎，只是為了爭論， 知道嗎，是假設的。
which one would you be willing to give up?
你要放棄哪一個？
Frank Jr. Jr.?
小小弗蘭克?
Well, it'd be great for my shoulder.
噢，你選了這麼好的一個。
You'd be getting a really good one.
He's really funny.
我是說，知道嗎，他真是太有趣了。
Like, the other day, he made up this joke:
比如，那天他說了個笑話
What's green and says, "Hey, I'm a frog"?
什麼東西是綠的並且說 「嗨，我是一隻青蛙」？
A talking frog.
一隻會說話的青蛙！
Oh, no, you can't have him, he's too funny.
噢，不，你不能帶他走。他太有意思了。
Well, all right, that's fine. What about Leslie?
好吧，好吧，沒問題。那萊絲莉呢？
Oh, no, no, not Leslie. No.
噢，不，不。不要是萊絲莉。
She's the only one that knows how to burp the alphabet.
不，她……她是唯一一個會 打著嗝說出字母表來的。
All right, so that leaves Chandler.
好吧，那就剩下錢德了。
No, no, you can't have Chandler. No, no. She's my little genius.
噢，不，不，你不能帶走錢德 不。不，不。她是個小天才。
I got big hopes for her.
我對她抱有很大期望。
She's gonna be a doctor or a realtor.
她會成為醫生或者房地產經紀人……
Wow, Frank, I think we just ran out of kids.
哇，弗蘭克。我想我誰都帶不走了。
Oh, I think you're right.
噢，我想你是對的。
Oh, wow. Phoebe, I don't think I can give one of them up.
哦，哇，菲比 我不認為我能放棄任何一個。
I mean, you know, they drive me crazy, but they're my babies.
我是說，知道嗎 他們讓我發瘋，可他們是我的孩子。
I'm sorry, Frank, I didn't realize things were so bad.
很抱歉，弗蘭克。我沒想到事情會這樣。
You know, I'll help out more. I can baby-sit anytime you want.
知道嗎，我會幫你的。 你需要的時候我可以照顧他們。
You name the day and I'll be there.
你說一天，我會去的。
- How about tomorrow? - Well, that's not good.
-明天怎麼樣？ -呃，不好。
But I can move some stuff around and I'll be there.
不過知道嗎，我會推掉其它事 我會到的。
You and Alice just take the whole day together.
你和愛麗絲可以整天呆在一起。
You'd do that for us?
你為我們這麼做？
Are you kidding? That's what sisters are for.
你開玩笑嗎？你以為姐姐是幹什麼的？
Oh, look at them.
看看他們！
I love you so much.
噢，我真愛你們。
Oh, crap, don't wake up! Don't wake up!
噢，天吶，別醒過來，別醒過來！
- Where are Bill and Colleen? - Kitchen, getting something to eat.
-比爾和克琳呢？ -他們在廚房弄點吃的。
Can you believe how nice they are?
您能想像他們有多好嗎？
We have to leave.
我們必須走！！
Why? What did you do in the bathroom?
為什麼？你在洗手間做了什麼？
I didn't get to the bathroom. I bumped into Owen on the way.
我還沒去洗手間呢。 我在路上碰到了歐文
He didn't know he was adopted. There's a slight chance..
可他還不知道他是被領養的。 有一個小小的機會
I may have told him.
我告訴了他。
Oh, my God, where's my purse? No, I can replace everything in there.
噢，天吶，我的手袋呢？ 不，我們把東西放在這兒。
- Get that binder and let's go! - Hi.
- 拿上活頁冊，走！ -嗨。
Some little snacks for everybody.
給大家的一點小吃。
You don't have to eat the sour worms. Those are for Owen.
哦，你們不用吃酸蠕蟲， 那是給歐文的。
I'll go get him in a second.
我一會兒去叫他。
By the way, you should know, we haven't told him he's adopted yet.
順便說一句， 你們該知道 我們還沒告訴他他是領養的。
But kids are so intuitive.
可孩子們直覺很靈敏。
Don't you think, on some level, he already knows?
你不認為某種程度上他已經知道了？
- I'm adopted? - See? Intuitive.
- 我是領養的？！ - 看？直覺！
What? Where did you hear that?
什麼？你從哪兒聽來的？
He told me.
他告訴我的！
And he paid me 50 dollars not to tell.
他還給我50塊錢讓我別說出來。
Which, technically, now you should give back.
那現在你該把錢還給我了！
You told him he's adopted?
你告訴他他是領養的？
I'm sorry. You should have a sign out there or something.
實在對不起，可你們應該在 那兒或者什麼地方寫明白。
Or at least whisper it to people when they come in the door.
或者在人們進門的時候悄悄告訴他們：
"Owen doesn't know he's adopted, and he also thinks Santa is real."
「歐文不知道他是領養的， 他也認為聖誕老人是真實存在的。」
He isn't?
他不是嗎？！
We have to get out of here, baby.
我們必須走了，親愛的！
What is the matter with you?
你怎麼了？
All right, look, I know what Chandler did was not the best..
好了, 聽著, 我知道 錢德做的不是最好的..
but anyone would assume that a 12-year-old has been told he's adopted.
但是任何人都應該想到 一個12歲的孩子會被告知是被領養的
- Yeah, he's 8. - Wow, he's tall.
- 是的, 他8歲. - 喔, 他長的好高.
What country did you get him from?
你從哪個國家領到他的?
Everyone, I would like to make a toast..
諸位，我要向
to Rachel and Joey.
瑞秋和喬伊敬酒。
And to love.
還有愛情。
Ah, love!
啊，愛情。
L-O-V-E. Love.
L-O-V-E，愛情。
L is for "life."
L是生活。
And what is life without love?
沒有愛情哪有生活？
Oh, my God, are we supposed to answer?
噢，我的天吶，我們要回答嗎？
O is for:
O是
"Oh, wow!"
「噢，哇！」
The V is for this..
V是
very surprising turn of events..
事情轉變的這麼快
which I am still fine with, by the way.
而順便說明，我完全應付得來。
E..
E是
is for how..
我發現
extremely normal I find it..
這是多麼的正常。
that you two..
你們倆
are together.
走到了一起。
And that one day you might get married..
有一天你們會結婚
and have children of your own.
還會有你們自己的孩子。
- Dude, are you okay? - Totally.
-夥計，你還好吧？ -完全沒問題。
Ross, you don't seem okay.
羅斯，你看起來不太好。
I'm sorry, it must be the pressure of entertaining.
對不起，一定是快樂的壓力太大了。
I think everyone would feel better if we had some flan.
我想如果我們吃點果餡餅會感覺好點。
Wait, Ross. Ross, I.. I have to take off.
等等，羅斯，我——我要走了。
- No! - I'm sorry.
- 不行！ - 對不起
I have an early class in the morning.
我明天早上還有一節很早的課，
But this has been lovely.
不過這已經很好了。
Wasn't it? And you thought it would be awkward with Joey.
是嗎？可你認為跟喬伊一起很不自在
And that you never really liked Rachel.
而且你從沒真正喜歡過瑞秋。
You are on fire! I'll call you in the morning, okay?
你過火了！ 我早上給你打電話，好嗎？
- Okay. - All right.
- 好吧。 - 好
God, Rachel, what Ross just said, that's just..
天吶，瑞秋，羅斯剛才說得簡直太……
That's okay. Girls tend not to like me.
噢，沒事，女孩們從來都不喜歡我。
Fine.
再見。
Okay. I guess it's just flan for three.
好吧，我想只需要給三個人吃的果餡餅了！
Hey, that rhymes.
嘿，嘿，這還挺押韻！
You know what, Ross, I think we're gonna take off too.
知道嗎，羅斯？ 我想我們也該走了。
Of course. God, I'm so stupid.
噢，噢，當然。天吶，我真蠢。
You guys are a couple now.
你們現在是一對了。
I mean, you probably just want to be alone.
我是說，你們可能想單獨呆著。
- No, it's just getting late.. - It's fine. It's totally fine.
-不，不，我只是說天晚了…… -嘿，嘿，沒事的。真的沒事。
I've got plenty of margaritas. It's all good.
我已經喝了夠多的瑪格麗塔。真得很好。
I don't even know what that's for.
我都不知道那是什麼。
You know what?
知道嗎？
I think I'm gonna stay here and make sure he's okay.
我想我應該留下保證他沒事。
- That's probably a good idea. - I'll see you in the morning.
-對，這可能是個好主意。 - 對，明天早上見。
Okay.
嗯嗯，好吧。
Yeah, you know, Joey, I..
知道嗎，喬伊
I don't think he's ever gonna be okay with this.
我不認為他會接受我們倆在一起。
It doesn't look good, does it?
看起來不太好，是嗎？
I guess I made Tater Tots.
我猜我做了Tater Tots.
Ross, oven mitts!
羅斯, 手套!
Morning.
早上好。
- Here you go. - Thanks.
-你醒了。 -謝謝
- Did you stay here all night? - Yeah.
-你整個晚上都在這兒? -對。
So you took off my pants and shoes?
你脫了我的褲子和鞋？
No. No, no.
不，不，不。
You actually did that when you were dancing to the Chicago soundtrack.
實際上是你和著《芝加哥》 的原聲跳舞時自己脫掉的。
Look, Ross..
聽著，羅斯
about Rachel and I. Listen, you don't have to worry about that..
關於我和瑞秋 聽著，你什麼都不用擔心，知道嗎？
because nothing's gonna happen.
因為什麼都不會發生。
What do you mean?
你是什麼意思？
She and I said from the beginning..
好吧，我們從一開始就說
we weren't gonna do anything unless you were okay with it.
如果你不接受的話我們什麼都不會做的。
And clearly..
而很明顯……
What are you talking about? I'm fine.
嘿，你在說什麼？我很好！
- Are we still doing this? - No.
- 我們可以繼續這樣? - 不可以.
It's okay, Ross. You know, I totally understand.
很好，羅斯，好嗎？ 我完全明白。
Of course you're not fine. You're..
你當然接受不了。你們是……
You're Ross and Rachel.
你們是羅斯和瑞秋
Yeah, except we're not.
除非我們不是。
I mean, we haven't been a couple in, like..
我是說，我們已經有，
six years.
6年沒在一起了。
My God, is that right?
噢，天吶，真的嗎？
Has it been that long?
有這麼久了?
That's what I hear, yeah.
我也是這麼聽說的，是的。
This is crazy. I mean, six years..
這太瘋狂了。我是說，6年？
and because of me, you guys aren't gonna be together?
就因為我，你們不能在一起？
Can I ask you something?
我能問你點事嗎？
Really..
說真的
what is this thing with you and Rachel?
你覺得跟瑞秋在一起怎麼樣？
Come on, you know me. You know..
別鬧了，我是說，你瞭解我，你知道……
Joey.
喬伊
I'm crazy about her.
我為她感到瘋狂。
And she feels the same way?
她也這麼想嗎？
I think so.
我想是的。
Well, then..
好吧，那麼
maybe it's time we all moved on.
可能現在我們都該往前看了。
Yeah, but, Ross, I mean, you're not okay with it, so..
對，不過，羅斯 我是說，你並沒有完全接受。
No, but I want to be.
不，我會的。
I will be.
嘿，我會的。
Besides, I'm with Charlie, right?
另外，我還有查莉呢，對吧？
Oh, my God, I'm still with Charlie, aren't I?
噢，天吶，我還跟查莉在一起呢, 是嗎？
- She didn't see the dance, did she? - No, no, no.
-我是說，她沒看見我跳舞吧？ -不，不，不，不
No, that was.. That was just for me.
只有——只有我看見了。
Hey, you..?
你。。
You sure about this?
你說真的？
Yeah, I'm sure.
對，我是說真的。
And..
那.. .
we're okay?
我們的關係沒問題嗎？
- Hey, Phoebe. - Hey.
- 嗨，菲比 - 嗨。
We just want to give you a heads up.
呃，我們只是想給你提個醒。
- Bill and Colleen hate us. - Why?
- 比爾和克琳討厭我們。 - 為什麼？
Owen didn't know he's adopted and Monica told him.
歐文不知道他是領養的， 可莫妮卡告訴了他。
What?
什麼？
- He didn't know? He's 12. - No, he's only 8.
- 他不知道?他12歲了啊. - 不, 他才8歲.
I'll bet he's Russian.
我打賭他是俄羅斯人.
Still, he had to find out sometime.
可是，他總有一天會發現的。
How would you like it if someone told the triplets that you gave birth to them?
對，可如果有人告訴這三胞胎 是你生了他們你會高興嗎？
I'm gonna go tell Emma she was an accident.
我要去告訴愛瑪，說她是個事故的結果。